A Battle Between God and Monster
Hulk vs. Thor is a action, animation, fantasy film directed by Sam Liu.
For ages, Odin has protected his kingdom of Asgard.
But every winter, the All-Father must rest and regain his strength for one week.
During this time, all of Asgard's foes (including trolls, giants, dark elves, and demons) try to claim the realm for their own,
but they are always stopped by Odin's son, the mighty Thor, albeit with the loss of many brave Asgardian warriors.
Loki, god of mischief, has kidnapped Dr.
Bruce Banner and brought him to Asgard with the help of Amora, once
Thor's lover, now the supervillain known as the Enchantress.
Loki makes Banner angry and he changes into the Hulk.
The Enchantress then casts a spell over the Hulk which separates Banner from his
monstrous alter-ego and grants Loki control over the Hulk's body.
Hulk (voice), played by Fred Tatasciore.
Loki (voice), played by Graham McTavish.
Thor (voice), played by Matthew Wolf.
Sif (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Bruce Banner (voice), played by Bryce Johnson.
Amora the Enchantress (voice), played by Kari Wahlgren.
Marvel Animated Features (MAF) is a series of eight American direct-to-video animated superhero films made by MLG
Productions, a joint venture between Marvel Studios (later Marvel Animation) and Lions Gate Entertainment.
The film explores themes of fight, superhero, based on
comic, norse mythology, superhuman strength.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.